[
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a value of the font-variant property in CSS?",
    "answers": {
      "answer_1": "normal",
      "answer_2": "small-caps",
      "answer_3": "large-caps",
      "answer_4": "inherit",
      "correct_answer": "large-caps"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following CSS property is used to specify whether the table cells share the common or separate border?",
    "answers": {
      "answer_1": "border-collapse",
      "answer_2": "border-radius",
      "answer_3": "border-spacing",
      "answer_4": "None of the above",
      "correct_answer": "border-collapse"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "The CSS property used to make the rounded borders, or rounded corners around an element is ....",
    "answers": {
      "answer_1": "border-collapse",
      "answer_2": "border-spacing",
      "answer_3": "border-radius",
      "answer_4": "None of the above",
      "correct_answer": "border-radius"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "The CSS property which is used to define the set the difference between two lines of your content is ....",
    "answers": {
      "answer_1": "min-height",
      "answer_2": "max-height",
      "answer_3": "line-height",
      "answer_4": "font-height",
      "correct_answer": "line-height"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following CSS property is used to set the blend mode for each background layer of an element?",
    "answers": {
      "answer_1": "background-blend-mode",
      "answer_2": "background-collapse",
      "answer_3": "background-transform",
      "answer_4": "background-origin",
      "correct_answer": "background-blend-mode"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "The correct syntax to give a line over text is :",
    "answers": {
      "answer_1": "text-decoration: line-through",
      "answer_2": "text-decoration: overline",
      "answer_3": "text-decoration: none",
      "answer_4": "text-decoration: underline",
      "correct_answer": "text-decoration: overline"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "The CSS property used to specify the transparency of an element is :",
    "answers": {
      "answer_1": "Hover",
      "answer_2": "overlay",
      "answer_3": "clearfix",
      "answer_4": "opacity",
      "correct_answer": "opacity"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which if the following CSS function allows us to perform calculations?",
    "answers": {
      "answer_1": "calc() function",
      "answer_2": "calculator() function",
      "answer_3": "calculate() function",
      "answer_4": "cal() function",
      "correct_answer": "calc() function"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of CSS is used in the below code?\n <p style = \"border:2px solid red;\">  ",
    "answers": {
      "answer_1": "Inline CSS",
      "answer_2": "Internal CSS",
      "answer_3": "External CSS",
      "answer_4": "None of the above",
      "correct_answer": "Inline CSS"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following CSS property defines how an image or video fits into container with established height and width?",
    "answers": {
      "answer_1": "object-fit",
      "answer_2": "object-position",
      "answer_3": "position",
      "answer_4": "None of the above",
      "correct_answer": "object-fit"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following selector in CSS is used to select the elements that do not match the selectors?",
    "answers": {
      "answer_1": ":! selector",
      "answer_2": ":not selector",
      "answer_3": ":empty selector",
      "answer_4": ":has selector",
      "correct_answer": ":not selector"
    }
  }
]
